这玩意儿真碍手碍脚
Well, that thing's clearly in the way.
好了
All right.
死冰箱
Damn fridge!
-乔伊  你好吗  -很好
- Hi, Joey. How you doing? - Great...
室友
...roomie.
-我们现在的确是室友  -没错
- l guess we are roommates now. - l know.
既然你都这么说了  我们的冰箱坏了
Yeah! Well, now that you bring it up. Our fridge is broken,
得买台新的
we have to get a new one.
我算了算你该付一半  谢谢400块
Now, I checked around and your half is $400. Thanks a lot.
我才不帮你摊一半呢
l'm not paying for half of that.
我只住到我们家那边整理好而已
I'm only staying here until my apartment gets fixed.
瑞秋  这台冰箱是我出生之后
Look, Rach, my parents bought this fridge
我父母买的  知道吗
just after l was born. Okay?
我用这么多年从没有过问题
Now, l have never had a problem with it.
你一来它就坏了
Then you show up and it breaks!
这意味着什么
What does that tell you?
冰箱无法和人一样长寿
That refrigerators don’t live as long as people.
你也知道自动提款机
All right, now you know that
一次只能提300块
the ATM will only lets you take out 300 at a time.
所以剩下的100块  你就用支票吧
So I'll take a check for the other hundred.
你在开玩笑吧
You're joking, right?
当然是在开玩笑啦  我不收支票
Of course l'm joking. l don't take checks.
幸好你长得帅
Thank God, you're pretty.
你们有认识帅哥吗
Do you guys know any cute guys?
当然有  我的好朋友乔伊就是啊
Well, of course I do! My good friend Joey over here.
我忘了  谢谢赞赏  钱德勒
l'm sorry. Thank you, Chandler.
周末有大型慈善晚会
Anyway, there's this big charity ball this weekend.
拉尔夫·劳伦买了一桌
And Ralph Lauren bought a table,
所以我得去
...so l kind of have to go.
-慈善募款的主题是什么  -不晓得
- What's the charity? - l don't know.
不是某种树  就是某种病...
Something, either trees or disease....
拉尔夫整天喃喃自语
Ralph mumbles a lot.
他是不是都趁你不专心时  故意喃喃自语
Does Ralph mumble when you're not paying attention?
对呀  好奇怪哦
Yeah. lt's weird.
总之我得找个男伴
But the thing is need to find a date.
你想找什么样的人呢
Well, what kind of guy are you looking for?
自己有晚礼服  或租得起晚礼服的人
Someone that has his own tux or the ability to rent a tux.
所以身家起码要有50元的男性
So he has to be a male who has at least $50.
只差一点
So close.
-大家好啊  -好啊
- Hey, everybody! - Hi, there.
-这是伊丽莎白  -你好  伊丽莎白
- This is Elizabeth. - Hi, Elizabeth.
我就是那个学生
l'm the student.
真可爱...才怪
lsn't she cute? Nope.
这可能不关我的事情
Y'know, this is probably none of my business,
但你们在一起
but, weren't you guys supposed to...
不是不能被人看到吗
...not be seen in public together?
我们不是一起的
We are not together.
我们只是两个
We're just two people
在咖啡馆巧遇的人
who happen to run into each other here at the coffee house.
这是...
This is....
真奸诈
Oh, sly!
我很想多认识你们  但是我得走了
l wanted to meet you guys, but l have to run.
-改天见  -好
- I'll see you later? - Okay.
-罗斯  再见  -再见
- Bye, Ross. - Bye. See you.
先生  我不是故意撞到你的
Oops! I did not mean to run into you like that sir.
女士  没关系的
That's quite all right, ma'am.
再见
Bye.
她为什么要走
So why is she leaving?
要上晚自习去赶作业吗
Is it a school night and she has a lot of homework to do?
对啊  她明天要交分子流行病学报告
Yes. Her molecular epidemiology paper is due tomorrow.
帮我祝她好运
Tell her good luck with that.
还有吗   别客气
Anyone else? Bring them on.
她什么时候生日
When's her birthday?
我不知道呢  瑞秋  怎么了
I don't know Rachel, why?
我只是好久没吃儿童生日餐了
Well, y'know, lt's just been so long since l've been to Chuck E. Cheese.
-我喜欢伊丽莎白  -谢谢
- l like Elizabeth. - Well, thanks.
我真的很喜欢她
In fact, l like her so much,
记得告诉她  今年我的女童军饼干要提早送
you tell her l want my cookies early this year.
来一盒薄荷口味和巧克力饼
A box of Thin Mints and some Tagalongs.
你们就别取笑他了
Come on you guys, give him a break.
罗斯  你们交往得怎样
Ross, seriously, how's it going with her?
非常好
Well, actually it’s been great.
她才二十岁  还不想定下来
She's 20,  so she’s not looking for anything too serious,
最适合现在的我
which is perfect for me right now.
太好了  她真的好像很不错
That's great. Seriously, she seems very nice.
谢谢  我知道你们喜欢取笑我
Thanks. I know you guys like to give me a hard time and all,
但我真的很希望你们能喜欢她
But it really means a lot to me that you like her.
只要知道你们...
Just knowing that you guys are like
我想到一个很棒的
Okay, l got a good one.
来咯
OK.
她是怎样  十二岁吗
What is she, like, 12?
钱德勒  你觉得关于我们感情的讨论够了吗
Chandler, do we talk about our relationship enough?
够了  有水果卷吗
Yeah. Do we have any Fruit Roll- Ups?
好啦
Okay.
我刚想到一个很适合当瑞秋男伴的人
I thought of the perfect guy for Rachel to take to her thing.
有意思  我们也找到人了
That's so funny. We found someone too.
那好  她可以在我的人和你们的怪胎之中
Good. She'll have a choice between my guy
选一个
and your weirdo.
为什么我们的人是怪胎
Why would our guy be a weirdo?
你们俩的眼光就这样嘛
Because that's just your taste.
瑞秋才不会选你的蠢人
See, Rachel's not gonna pick your stupid guy.
-是吗  -没错
- Yeah? - Yeah.
我的人是律师  还当义工
My guy is a lawyer, who does volunteer work.
而且他有这个东西
And he has one of these.
脸屁股吗
A face ass?
下巴窝啦
A chin dimple.
我们这个是钱德勒的同事
Well, you know, our guy works with Chandler.
人好聪明又会打扮
He's really nice and smart, and he's a great dresser.
你们看过他的身体吗
Have you seen your guy's body?
没有  他是一颗飘来飘去的头
No. Our guy's just a floating head.
我这个身材很赞  他是我的客人
Well, my guy is spectacular. He's a massage client.
有一次他在按摩台上
And one time, when he was on the table,
我看过了  整个看光光哦
l looked at it. And l mean all of it.
偷看客人是不对的
You're not supposed to look.
难道还专门有警察抓我偷看吗
Oh yeah, like there are police for that!
你还会偷看啊   你给我按摩过呢
Wait. You look? You massaged me.
没错
l know.
好  你那个或许身材很好
All right fine, your guy may have a great body,
但我们这个很风趣
but our guy is really funny.
钱德勒式的风趣吗
Chandler funny?
-我们这个舞功高强  -我这个饱读诗书
- Our guy's a great dancer. - My guy's well- read.
-我们这个发质很好  -我这个牙齿漂亮
- Our guy has great hair. - My guy has great teeth.
我们这个体香香得不得了
Our guy smells incredible.
你是想他变成你男人吗
Do you want our guy to be your guy?
你的脸色不太好  乔伊
Well, you don't look good, Joe.
冰箱坏了  我得把东西都吃掉
The fridge broke, so l had to eat everything.
冷盘  冰激凌  莱姆...
Cold cuts, ice cream, limes.
那咖啡色罐子里是什么
What was in that brown jar?
-那个还在啊  -现在不在了
- That's still in there? - Not anymore.
总之你要怎么付钱给我
So anyway, how do you want to pay me?
你要为我提供某种服务吗
ls this a service you're providing me?
不是  是我要买冰箱  我们的冰箱
No, for my new fridge. For our new fridge.
什么我们的新冰箱
Our new fridge?
-我已经不住这里了  -那又怎样
- l don't live here anymore. - So what?
你看  假设我们是离婚夫妻
Look, okay, suppose we were a divorced couple.
我取得孩子的监护权  对吧
And l got custody of the kid. Right?
结果孩子死了  我总得买个新孩子吧
Now suppose the kid dies and l gotta buy a new kid.
好
Okay.
给我400块
Give me $400!
盖勒教授
Professor Geller?
我不认识这个学生
Oh, a student l don't know.
我能不能跟您谈一下
l was wondering if l could talk to you for a moment?
当然可以  是哪方面的事
Yes, of course. What would this be regarding?
在你的办公室亲热
Making out in your office.
好  我们进去再说
Of course. Why don't we go inside.
-怎么了  -门把
- What? - Doorknob.
抱歉
Sorry.
我真的有事要跟你说
l actually do need to talk to you.
什么事
Ok. What-what about?
-春假的事  -春假的事
- Spring vacation? - Spring vacation?
对  学校没课
Yeah, we have time off,
很多人都要一起去旅行...
and a lot of people are going on trips...
-盖勒教授  -是  菲森死盯个乐教授
- Professor Geller. - Yes, Professor Friesenstinlender.
我马上就好
l'll be with you in one moment.
那我就买一盒薄荷巧克力饼
So l will take one box of the Thin Mints.
你们不懂
You don't understand.
伊丽莎白想找我跟她去旅行
Elizabeth was about to ask me to go on a trip with her.
这样叫慢慢来吗   我还没准备好
ls that taking it slow? l'm not ready for this.
知道吗  我该怎么跟她说
Okay? What do l tell her?
实话实说  说你还没准备好
Tell her the truth, tell her you're not ready.
可以试试
l could do that.
要是她不高兴呢
What if she gets upset?
那你就拿芭比娃娃逗她
Then you distract her with a Barbie doll.
或者你也可以...
Or you could just, you know, you....
你搞什么鬼啊
What the hell are you doing?
我干什么   你弄坏我的冰箱
What the hell am l doing? You just broke my fridge!
什么   怎么
What? How do...?
你怎么知道它坏了
How do you know it's even broken?
它怎么坏的我会不知道吗
You think l don't know what breaks my fridge?
你等一下
Excuse me!
猜猜怎么着了
Well, what do you know?
坏了
Broken!
请赔400块
That'll be $400.
乔伊  我看见你推他了
Joey, l saw you push him.
是你推的
You pushed him.
乔伊  我没把它弄坏
Joey, l did not break this. Okay?
它已经坏一阵子了
That has been broken for a while.
钱德勒  还记得我提过我们的冰箱的事吗
All right. Chandler. Remember l told you about our fridge?
我还没拿到你该出的钱呢
l still haven't gotten the check for your half yet.
不要给他钱
Do not give him any money!
你少插嘴  你撞坏我的冰箱
l'm not talking to you! You broke my fridge!
盖勒教授  你找我吗
You wanted to see me, Professor Geller?
是的  请进
Yes. Please come in.
-门把  -对  还有点玩上瘾了
- Doorknob? - Yeah. lt kind of grows on you.
我想继续上次春假的话题
l wanted to finish talking to you about spring vacation.
好
Good.
听我说  我...
Look, l....
我跟你在一起很开心
Look, l'm having a great time with you.
我不想进展得太快
And l just don't want us to move too fast
或是给我们太多压力
or put too much pressure on us.
所以很抱歉  我们还不能一起旅行
So l'm sorry, l just don't think we should go away together yet.
太快了
lt's too soon.
罗斯  你误会我的意思了
Ross, l think you misunderstood what l was saying.
我只是想告诉你
l just wanted to tell you
我要去佛罗里达几星期
that l'm going to Florida for a couple weeks.
不
No.
是你误会我的意思了
l think you misunderstood what l was saying.
我的意思是...
What l meant was...
你好可爱哦
You are so adorable.
这个  我们来讨论这个
That. Let's talk about that.
你跟伊丽莎白谈得怎样
How did it go with Elizabeth?
没事  只是一场误会
Fine. Just a misunderstanding.
她没有要找我去
She didn't want me to go with her.
她只是要告诉我
She just wanted to let me know
她春假要去佛罗里达
she's going to Florida for a spring vacation.
等等  她是去放春假
Wait a minute. ls she going for spring vacation
还是去春游
or spring break? Wahoo!
有什么差别
What's the difference?
春假是跟爷爷奶奶共享天伦
Spring vacation, you're doing nice things with your grandparents.
春游是跟兄弟会的人上床
Spring break, you're doing frat guys.
知道吗   并非每个人的春游都那样
You know what? Not all spring breaks are like that.
-你做了什么  -我跟我爸去埃及
- What did you do on yours? - l went to Egypt with my dad.
我可以想像  "爸  看那人面狮身像"
l can see it now. ''Look, Dad, it's the Sphinx, wahoo!''
伊丽莎白那么正经
l think Elizabeth is a little more serious than
不会去"春游"
"Spring break, wahoo!"
拜托  她修了我的课
All right? I mean she’s taken my class!
-还跟教授上床  -我去打给她
- And slept with the professor. - l'm gonna call her.
各位  这是塞巴斯提安
You guys, l want you to meet Sebastian.
我们刚刚在报摊认识
We met at the newsstand.
我们都买了《原野与河流》
We both grabbed for the last Field and Stream.
什么   我有在看啊
What? l read that.
-你要咖啡吗  -是的  谢谢
- Can l get you a cup of coffee? - Yes. Thank you.
-瑞秋  你这是什么意思  -什么
- Rachel, what the hell is this? - What?
你叫我们帮你找人
You ask us to find a guy,
却自己从大街上拉了一个人回来
and you come traipsing in here with a guy of your own?
你们帮我找到人了啦
You found me a guy?
对  我们在钱德勒的公司
Yes. We found you a really cute,
相中一个可爱风趣的人
funny guy from Chandler's work.
我也找到了  不是他们的那种怪胎
Yeah, and l found you one too, who is not a weirdo.
你们知道吗   真是谢谢你们
You know what though, guys, l really appreciate that...
不过我带塞巴斯提安去就好了
but I think I’m just gonna take Sebastian to the charity.
你确定吗   我们这个人选很香喔
Are you sure?! Because our guy smells incredible!
别再提那个了  好吗
Would you stop it with that already?
-你的咖啡  -谢谢
- Here you go. - Thank you.
塞巴斯提安  你有在当义工吗
So, Sebastian, do you do any volunteer work?
-没有  怎么了  -没事
- No, not really. Why? - No reason.
我只是有认识一个关心别人的单身汉
It's just l know a single guy who does care about other people.
你风趣吗
Are you funny?
-什么  -你们在干什么
- Excuse me? - What are you guys doing?
你风趣吗   讲个笑话来听
Are you funny? Tell us a joke!
我只是想和瑞秋喝杯咖啡
Look, l just wanted to have coffee with Rachel.
很多人都想
Well, so do a lot of people.
-老实说我该走了  -但是..
- Actually, l gotta get going. - But you...
有空打电话给我
Give me a call sometime.
你没给我电话号码
You didn't give me your phone number.
好  那就改天见
Okay, see you later.
原来他蛮风趣的
Turns out he is kind of funny.
你们真是太乱来了
l cannot believe you guys!
他人很好  却被你们赶走了
He was really nice, and he just left because of you!
塞巴斯提安   那是猫的名字吗
Yeah, but "Sebastian"? What is that, a cat's name?
瑞秋  猜我发现什么
You know what l noticed, Rachel?
他很容易被吓到
He scares easy.
你想带这种人参加舞会吗
ls that the kind of guy you wanna take to a ball?
"塞巴斯提安  要不要跳舞"
"Hey, Sebastian, would you like to dance?"
"好  我得走了"
"Okay. l gotta go. "
别再说了  瑞秋  对不起
Stop it. Rachel, we're very sorry.
我知道我们这样做很不对
that is a very insensitive thing for us to do.
让我们补偿你
And y’know what? Let us make it up to you,
我们有两个好男人让你挑
we have two really great guys for you.
对啊  你有什么损失
Yeah, what have you got to lose?
搞不好会认识让你心动的人
Y'know, you might even end up with someone really special.
如果你选我这边的话
lf you pick my guy.
-好吧  -你愿意见我们找的人
- All right. - Okay. So you will meet our guys?
我愿意
Yes, I'll meet 'em.
你要选谁都行  由你自己决定
lt doesn't matter which one you choose. It’s completely up to you.
我们这个很完美
Our guy is perfect.
或者你也可以选
Or you could go out with the guy
那个连菲比自己看不上眼的人
Phoebe deemed not good enough for herself.
菲比  你在这里  你弄坏我的冰箱
Pheebs! There you are! OK. You broke my fridge.
欠我400块
You owe me $400.
-好吧  -真的
- Okay, sure. - Really?
你还欠我六百块  作为我给你前十次试镜
Technically, you owe me $600 for sending out happy thoughts...
出点子的报酬
...on your last 10 auditions.
那就扯平了
Call it even?
好吧
Okay.
回来了
There you are.
伊丽莎白怎么说
What did Elizabeth say?
她真的是要去代托纳春游
Turns out she is going to Daytona for "spring break, wahoo. "
也就是有湿T恤美女选拔赛
That means wet T- shirt contests,
男生在女生身上喝酒
guys doing shots off of girls' bodies...
在陌生人身边醒来
waking up next to people you don’t even know…
她会玩得超爽爽
Ang she is gonna have a great time!
她要住科罗娜饭店吗
ls she staying at the Hotel Corona?
你熟悉那里的饭店吗
You know the hotels?
当然  我参加过八一年的春游
Sure!sl was there! Spring Break '81 , wahoo!
八一年你才十三岁呢
ln 1 981 , you were 1 3.
那又怎样  我开车去卖T恤  玩得好开心
So what? l drove down, sold T- shirts. Had a blast.
你们知道谁最会疯吗
You know who knows how to party?
喝醉的女大学生
Drunk college chicks.
好  她不能去
Okay, she can't go.
罗斯  你不能叫她不要去
Ross, you can't tell her not to go.
你们才交往没多久
You just started dating.
那我该怎么办
Then what am l supposed to do?
没办法  你只能接受事实
Nothing. You just have to be cool with it.
要是她跑去跟一堆人上床呢
What if she goes down there and sleeps with a bunch of guys?
那这次你就别娶她了呗
Well, maybe you don't marry this one.
你能去旅行真是好事
l'm so glad you're going on this trip.
就是啊  我这学期那么用功
Yeah. l've been working so hard this semester.
很需要疯狂一下  纾解压力
I really need to go crazy y’know, blow off some steam.
当然  当然
Sure. Sure.
我不知道你的计划底定了没
Look, l don't know if your plans are finalized yet, but...
还有一个办法可以纾解压力
...l know a great way to blow off steam.
-什么办法  -你喜欢做手工艺吗
- What? - Are you into crafts at all?
罗斯  你还好吗
Ross, are you okay?
我当然很好
Yeah. Of course l'm okay.
我只是在表示支持
l'm just being supportive.
支持你和这次旅行
Supportive of you and this whole trip...
还有这是什么
...and what's this?
那是泳衣
lt's a bathing suit?
你要穿它去见人吗
To wear in front of people?
这样叫支持吗
ls that supportive?
这样是吗
ls this?
太好了
Okay, good.
很高兴你答应见我们找的人
We're so glad you decided to meet our guy.
你一定会很喜欢他
You'll like him so much.
-你要什么时候见他  -不晓得
- So, when do you want to meet him? - l don't know.
我知道我明天晚上不用加班
I know I don’t work late tomorrow night.
明天晚上不错...  就明晚吧
Tomorrow night is good. Tomorrow night is good.
不过为什么现在能做的事
But but uh, y’know what? Why put off something till tomorrow
要拖到明天呢
that you could do it right now?
-伊尔达  过来  -什么
- Eldad, come here! - What?
-伊尔达  这是瑞秋  -你好吗
- Eldad, This is Rachel. - How are you?
有点措手不及  不过还不错
Well-well a little blind sided but y’know good.
伊尔达  坐  你坐过去
Eldad, sit down. Move over! Move over now!
这就对了
There you go. There you are.
好  我们知道了
Okay, we can take a hint!
你来干什么
What? What are you doing here?
这位是派翠克
This is Patrick.
你来晚了  她跟我们那个在一起了
OK. You're too late because she's already with our guy.
天啊  没错  我是来晚了
Oh my God, you’re right! I am too late;
他们正坐在沙发上聊天呢
They're sitting on the couch and talking.
来
Come on.
瑞秋  这是派翠克
Rachel? This is Patrick.
-你好  -你好
- Hi. - Hi.
他就是我说的那个人
This is the guy l was telling you about.
相信我
Yeah. And believe me,
这套西装太委屈里面的身材了
this suit does not do justice to what’s underneath it.
好
Okay.
但是菲比  我现在有点事
But, Pheebs, l'm just sort of in the middle of something.
好  没关系  你坐
Okay. That's okay. Have a seat.
-你不能这样  -我走好了
- You can't do that! - Maybe l should go.
坐下  我们占上风
Sit down, we're winning.
也许我才应该走
Maybe l should go.
不要  坐下
No. Have a seat!
瑞秋  你还没摸过伊尔达的头发呢
Rachel, you haven't touched Eldad's hair.
-超柔顺的  你摸摸看  -不必了
- He has the softest hair. Touch it. - l'm good.
瑞秋  派翠克很有钱  拿钱给她
Rachel, Patrick is really rich. Give her some money.
菲比  这个免费按摩的代价太高了
Y’know what Phoebe? This isn’t really worth the free massage.
-没错  派翠克再见  -不
- That’s right Patrick, bye-bye! - No!
伊尔达合作多了  而且很会跳舞
Eldad is much more cooperative, and he can dance.
你跳舞给瑞秋看
You dance for Rachel.
不  拜托不要
Don't dance for me. Please!
你们是怎么搞的
What is the matter with you guys?
没错  大家来说清楚
Yeah, OK. Let's talk it out.
只有我一个人觉得尴尬吗
Am l the only one that this is embarrassing for?
我也有点尴尬
l'm a little embarrassed.
老实说  该尴尬的是你们
l'll tell you who should be embarrassed. lt's you guys.
拜托  这也太扯了
Come on! This is ridiculous!
谢谢你们
Thank you very much,
但我不需要你们帮我找人
l do not need you to get me a date.
-那你为什么叫我们...  -我还没说完
- Why did she ask us to...? - l am still talking!
你们还把我真正喜欢的人赶走
Then you chase away the one guy l actually liked.
我没有冒犯的意思  真的  恭喜你
No offense to you guys. Really, congratulations on...
有那么多现金
...all the cash.
还有你...你的头发真的很柔顺
And you really do have very soft hair.
但我宁可自己参加晚会
But l'd much rather go to the ball all by myself
也不要再受这种气
than go through any more of this.
再见
Goodbye.
好了  你有用什么特别的润发乳吗
Now, do you use some sort of special conditioner on that hair?
木瓜粹取液
Yes. Papaya extract.
谢谢
Thank you.
好好去玩吧
So have a great time down there.
-我会的  -好
- l will. - Yeah.
-你有带那套泳衣吗  -有
- Did you pack that bathing suit? - Yeah.
我刚才把它藏起来  实在蛮好笑的
lt was pretty funny when l hid it for a while.
总之...
Anyway.
我担心那套泳装
l am worried about that bathing suit.
不是因为它太暴露  这一点我不在意
Not because it's revealing, which l'm fine with.
我是关心你的健康
l'm concerned about your health.
怕你晒到
Sun exposure.
放心  我带了一大堆防晒油
Don't worry, l have plenty of sun block.
-防晒系数30  -好吧
- lt's SPF 30. - All right.
如果真的有30就好了
Well, if what's in the bottle is actually 30.
有时候是30  有时候只有4
I mean, sometimes you get 30, sometimes it's 4
我发誓有很多都只是牛奶
and I swear to God more often than not it’s just milk.
罗斯  你放心
Ross, it's gonna be okay.
我不是要去跟一堆男生鬼混
l'm not going down there to hook up with a bunch of guys.
我很喜欢你
l really like you.
我也喜欢我们的关系
l like how things are going between us.
-真的吗  -对啊
- Really? - Yeah.
我只是去放松一下  跟朋友们玩一玩
l'm just going down there to relax and hang out with my friends.
好吧  酷
Okay. Cool.
他们来了
Here they are!
打电话给我
Call me!
瑞秋  抱歉把那些人硬塞给你
Rachel, sorry for pushing those guys on you.
没关系  后来我玩得很开心
That's all right. l ended up having a really good time.
晚会很成功
You know, the charity was a big success,
募到很多款  引起很多重视
and they raised a lot of money and awareness.
它是为什么募款
So, what was it for anyway?
我很想说貌似是一种疾病
l wanna say a disease.
罗斯留了奇怪的留言
l just got this really weird message from Ross.
叫我们看MTV台
He said to turn on MTV.
天啊  看  是伊丽莎白
Oh, my God, look! That's Elizabeth!
盖勒教授
Professor Geller.
重温13岁的旧梦呀
To be 13 again....